{
    "id": "f3a1ada2efc84585ba9c87fca3899150",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Does a dog make a ……………………….. pet than a cat?",
            "description": "Use a comparative adjective before than.",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "gooder"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f096c5726d7c41e7a3099464e6735deb"
        },
        {
            "question": "The pessimism in his writing is …………………………… depressing.",
            "description": "We use too to talk about undesirable extremes.",
            "answers": [
                "such",
                "so",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "cec5c44cceec47169bb0cccb06fa19ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "She takes a perverse delight in disagreeing ………………………… everyone.",
            "description": "We agree/disagree with a person.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4966c1147477415fa2c361cea33ad2d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is perfectly capable ………………………… care of herself.",
            "description": "We use of + ing form after capable.",
            "answers": [
                "to take",
                "to taking",
                "of taking"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "50ec6173556842eb9b6b900edc82fb55"
        },
        {
            "question": "She makes ……………………………. visits to the beauty parlor.",
            "description": "Periodic means regular or frequent.",
            "answers": [
                "periodic",
                "periodical",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbda9e77ad8341ccb9628eb717a35758"
        },
        {
            "question": "The library subscribes to scores of ……………………………….",
            "description": "Periodicals means magazines or journals.",
            "answers": [
                "periodics",
                "periodicals"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7ed8c22981954b7a876cd7ef78146796"
        },
        {
            "question": "Should parents be strict or ………………………….?",
            "description": "Permissive means lenient or indulgent.",
            "answers": [
                "permissible",
                "permissive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f00f46356adb4dfab81d785ecab4d7fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. hardships, she persisted in her efforts to get a college education.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "In spite",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96ac29a142f54eeb846b19e7b815bd8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He jumped up, ………………………….. his hat and ran to the bus stop.",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, we usually use a past tense in the subordinate clauses as well.",
            "answers": [
                "grabs",
                "grabbed",
                "grabbing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c260adbe577416c8412683ed41a2d7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "This belt won’t go …………………………… my waist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "around"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3df8119215394b8aba7c6451b29cb589"
        },
        {
            "question": "During a gasoline shortage, big cars ………………………… a glut on the market.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts. ",
            "answers": [
                "become",
                "became",
                "becomes"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c8e2a31a04844316b345ed959ddb20a0"
        }
    ]
}